https://AndrewCroy.Dev

https://github.com/Tadashi-Croy/

www.linkedin.com/in/andrewtcroy/ (248) 210-4398 • TadashiCroy@gmail.com

SUMMARY:

Six year Nuclear Navy maintenance technician and Junior Full Stack Developer specializing in Python and Javascript. Post Full-Stack development coding boot camp graduate, well versed in High Stress and Critical Environments as well as Technical Writing, Engineering Practices and Troubleshooting Methodologies. Experienced in multiple disciplines such as Automation, Testing and Data Analysis. Strong Leadership Fundamental, Project Management Experience and Communications Skills.

- HTML/CSS
- JQuery/Bootstrap
- Stress Management

- Python/Django
- Creative Problem Solver
- Vue.JS

- Automation
- Fast Learner
- Javascript

EXPERIENCE:

Freelance Developer:

October 2020 - Present:

• Worked with small businesses to create Full-Stack websites using Vue.js, HTML/CSS, Javascript, Python and Django.

Senior Engineering Technician, Meggitt-OECO

Meggitt is a British international company specializing in components and sub-systems for the aerospace, defense and selected energy markets.

Feb 2019 – Present:

- Lead Engineering technician on the New Product Integration Team, resulting in over 95% on time status for all deliverables.
- Programmed and installed multiple Vibration analysis control system software as the lead Vibration technician.
- Automated testing equipment using Python, Labview and proprietary OEM data logging software.
- Designed and repaired custom test fixtures to facilitate On Time Delivery of production materials.

Field Service Engineer, ASM

ASM is a multinational corporation that specializes in design, manufacturing, marketing and service of semiconductor equipment for the fabrication of semiconductor devices through atomic layer deposition, epitaxy, chemical vapor deposition and diffusion.

Mar 2018 - Feb 2019:

- Performed installations, preventative maintenance, remedial repair maintenance and failure analysis on complex electronic and electro-mechanical equipment.
- Troubleshot and maintained low pressure and atmospheric chemical diffusion furnaces, resulting in over 90% up time on the A412
- Created and maintained a high level of customer satisfaction through advanced customer service skills, implementing fast, quality responses to internal and external customers while maintaining a safety first mentality.

Nuclear Electrician, US Navy:

Feb 2012 - Feb 2018

Auxiliary Work Center Supervisor, U.S. Navy (Jan 2017- Feb2018)

- Managed and trained five technicians in thermal imaging and vibration analysis.
- Troubleshot and coordinated the replacement of bearings; advised multiple departments on necessary upgrades and repairs.
- Implemented risk mitigation processes to test electrical tools and systems, ensuring zero incidents and compliance with safety policies and regulations.

Maintenance Technician. U.S. Navy (Sep 2014 – Mar 2016)

- Conducted preventative and corrective maintenance to four 4160 volt generators while executing quarterly quality assurance inspections.
- Tested and troubleshot large and small industrial equipment; minimizing critical equipment downtime and failure in high stress environments.

TRAINING AND EDUCATION:

PDX Code Guild/Full Stack Intensive Course

• 14 week program which includes 420+ hours of developing software using Python, Javascript, Vue.js, Django, SQLite, HTML, CSS and agile workflow, along with skills to work effectively in a group/team to achieve goals (Pair Programming).

Syracuse University IVMF, Project Management Course

Completed a specialized course focusing on project management principles from the Project Management Institute

Naval Education:

Nuclear Propulsion Plant Operator Course (Prototype):

Completed 6 months of advanced nuclear prototype training which required the safe operation of a naval nuclear propulsion plant during startups, shutdowns, transient operations, and casualty scenarios.

Nuclear Power School:

Completed advanced courses in math, heat transfer, chemistry, physics, radiological controls, material science, reactor dynamics, and mechanical engineering fundamentals in the design, operation, and maintenance of naval nuclear propulsion plants with distinction.

Nuclear Field A School:

Completed courses on electrical safety lock-out and tag-out fundamentals, basic electrical theory, electronics, motors and preventative and corrective maintenance procedures with distinction.

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Programmable Logic Controllers- Certificate, Surface Warfare Officer's School, Norfolk, Virginia
- Level 3 Field Service Certification A412- ASM Global Training Center, Phoenix AZ